{
    "id": "0a579c739c56422f9cddc515e782d60c",
    "title": "Early and soon | Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0d490d3da4e04388801a95e82f68b968",
            "title": "Early or Soon | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I don’t like to get up ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "soon",
                        "early"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Bye Charlie, see you ………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susie left her office at 6 o’clock, so she should be here ………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "soon",
                        "early"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The government is expected to announce revised tax policies ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I arrived …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could you finish this job as ………………. as possible?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is in her ………………. twenties.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My parents immigrated to Canada in the ..................... 1980s.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look at the sky. It is going to rain ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Get well ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "early",
                        "soon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}